[
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "",
    "back": ""
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "A document created after the war that gave the colonists their independence.",
    "back": "Treaty of Paris"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "What is Barak Obama was, areing??",
    "back": "Obamacare,"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "Who was the first president of the United States?",
    "back": "George Washington"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "",
    "back": ""
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "text": "The United States was founded in the year 1776.",
    "cloze": "1776"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "A person who supported the British during the American Revolution.",
    "back": "Loyalist"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "He was a delegate from Virginia at the Second Continental Congress and wrote the Declaration of Independence. He later served as the third President of the United States.",
    "back": "Thomas Jefferson"
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "text": "Haw many letters, in Go...le  word???(number)",
    "cloze": "6"
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "text": "One of the events that lead to the Revolutionary War was the Boston Massacre where 5 colonists were killed by British soldiers.",
    "cloze": "Boston Massacre"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "",
    "back": ""
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "text": "President of the Continental Congress, John Hancock was first to sign the Declaration of Independence.",
    "cloze": "John Hancock"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "fred is green?",
    "back": "nopamn"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "",
    "back": ""
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "text": "Benjamin Franklin was an American patriot, writer, printer, and inventor. During the Revolutionary War he persuaded the French to help the colonists.",
    "cloze": "Benjamin Franklin"
  }
]